BU Records: Office of the President, Chancellor and President Emeritus: William Richardson White, Inclusive: 1936-1977, undated, Bulk: 1950-1969, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Personal Papers, 1936-1977, undated; 3
  - Awards, 1946-1977; 6
    - Christian Life Commission Plaque, 1974 (Box 222, Folder 9)
    - Certificate of Membership to Baylor University Council for Institutional Development, 1967 (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Certificate of Texas Ambassador of Goodwill, 1959 June (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Dr. White Awards, 1952-1963 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - Dr. White Awards, 1970-1977 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - Dr. White’s Hardin-Simmons University Diploma, 1953 (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - Dr. White Various Awards, 1960, 1962, 1967 (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - Edna White’s Howard Payne College Diploma, 1916 May 31 (Box 285 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Edna White’s Diploma from Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1922 May 26 (Box 285 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Freemason Certificate Pouch, 1953 November (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - Honorary Vice President, State Fair of Texas Medal, 1960 (Box 223, Folder 7)
    - Masonic Certificates, 1921, 1953 (Box 285 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Society Certificates, 1946-1947 (Box 223, Folder 8)
    - Tenth Anniversary Greetings, 1958 February 1 (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - Texas House of Representatives Resolution for Dr. White, 1977 March 31 (Box 223, Folder 9)
    - Texas State Senate Resolution No. 299, 1972 (Box 223, Folder 10)
    - Various, 1924, 1963-1964, undated (Box 285 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Waco Consistory Award, 1965 (Box 223, Folder 11)
  - Subject Files, 1946-1976, undated; 7
    - Airlines, 1953-1954 (Box 223, Folder 12)
    - American Morality and Nuclear Diplomacy, 1961 October 27 (Box 223, Folder 13)
    - Americanism 1, 1960 (Box 223, Folder 14)
    - Americanism 2, 1960 (Box 223, Folder 15)
    - Anti-Alcohol “War on Drugs”, undated (Box 285 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - April 1961 Travel Expenses, 1961 April (Box 223, Folder 16)
    - Bill Wallace of China, undated (Box 223, Folder 17)
    - Birthday Party Dr. White, 1976 (Box 223, Folder 18)
    - Books (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 223, Folder 19)
    - Books (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 223, Folder 20)
    - Books and Magazines, 1961 (Box 223, Folder 21)
    - Book of the Month (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 223, Folder 22)
    - Book of the Month (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 223, Folder 23)
    - Book: Building A Life by Minyard Barnett, 1966 (Box 223, Folder 24)
    - Cards Etc. Regarding Car Accident (1 of 3), 1962 (Box 223, Folder 25)
    - Cards Etc. Regarding Car Accident (2 of 3), 1962 (Box 223, Folder 26)
    - Cards Etc. Regarding Car Accident (3 of 3), 1962 (Box 223, Folder 27)
    - Carr P. Collins Clippings (1 of 2), undated (Box 223, Folder 28)
    - Carr P. Collins Clippings (2 of 2), undated (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - Capitol Punishment, 1961 (Box 224, Folder 2)
    - Catholic, 1960 (Box 224, Folder 3)
    - Christianity vs. Communism, 1954-1955 (Box 224, Folder 4)
    - Church and State (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - Church and State (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 224, Folder 6)
    - Citizens National Bank, 1960-1961 (Box 224, Folder 7)
    - The Citizens National Bank of Waco, 1959-1960 (Box 224, Folder 8)
    - Clippings 1, undated (Box 224, Folder 9)
    - Clippings 2, undated (Box 224, Folder 10)
    - Clippings (1 of 5), 1948-1950 (Box 224, Folder 11)
    - Clippings (2 of 5), 1948-1950 (Box 224, Folder 12)
    - Clippings (3 of 5), 1948-1950 (Box 224, Folder 13)
    - Clippings (4 of 5), 1948-1950 (Box 224, Folder 14)
    - Clippings (5 of 5), 1948-1950 (Box 224, Folder 15)
    - Clippings, 1950 (Box 224, Folder 16)
    - Clippings, 1951-1952 (Box 224, Folder 17)
    - Clippings (1 of 2), 1954-1955 (Box 224, Folder 18)
    - Clippings (2 of 2), 1954-1955 (Box 224, Folder 19)
    - Clippings, 1955, 1959 (Box 224, Folder 20)
    - Clippings (1 of 3), 1955-1956 (Box 224, Folder 21)
    - Clippings (2 of 3), 1955-1956 (Box 224, Folder 22)
    - Clippings (3 of 3), 1955-1956 (Box 224, Folder 23)
    - Clippings (1 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 224, Folder 24)
    - Clippings (2 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 224, Folder 25)
    - Clippings, 1957 (Box 224, Folder 26)
    - Clippings (1 of 3), 1958-1959 (Box 224, Folder 27)
    - Clippings (2 of 3), 1958-1959 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Clippings (3 of 3), 1958-1959 (Box 225, Folder 2)
    - Clippings (1 of 3), 1961 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - Clippings (2 of 3), 1961 (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - Clippings (3 of 3), 1961 (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - Clippings (1 of 3), 1961-1964 (Box 225, Folder 6)
    - Clippings (2 of 3), 1961-1964 (Box 225, Folder 7)
    - Clippings (3 of 3), 1961-1964 (Box 225, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 1964 (Box 225, Folder 9)
    - Committee on the Judiciary House of Representatives, 1961 August 24-30 (Box 225, Folder 10)
    - Communism (1 of 2), 1960-1963 (Box 225, Folder 11)
    - Communism (2 of 2), 1960-1963 (Box 225, Folder 12)
    - Conference Materials (For Speaking), 1976 (Box 225, Folder 13)
    - Book: The Cream Book with Clippings, undated (Box 225, Folder 14)
    - Current Race Track Gambling Clippings and Articles (1 of 10), undated (Box 225, Folder 15)
    - Current Race Track Gambling Clippings and Articles (2 of 10), undated (Box 225, Folder 16)
    - Current Race Track Gambling Clippings and Articles (3 of 10), undated (Box 225, Folder 17)
    - Current Race Track Gambling Clippings and Articles (4 of 10), undated (Box 225, Folder 18)
    - Current Race Track Gambling Clippings and Articles (5 of 10), undated (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - Current Race Track Gambling Clippings and Articles (6 of 10), undated (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - Current Race Track Gambling Clippings and Articles (7 of 10), undated (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - Current Race Track Gambling Clippings and Articles (8 of 10), undated (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - Current Race Track Gambling Clippings and Articles (9 of 10), undated (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - Current Race Track Gambling Clippings and Articles (10 of 10), undated (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - Daily Engagement Sheets, 1956 (Box 226, Folder 7)
    - Daily Engagement Sheets, 1957 (Box 226, Folder 8)
    - December, 1960 (Box 226, Folder 9)
    - Development Statistical Information, 1964 (Box 226, Folder 10)
    - Editorial Clippings about Dr. Frank Stanton, undated (Box 226, Folder 11)
    - Expenses, 1960 November-December (Box 226, Folder 12)
    - Expenses (1 of 2), 1956-1958 (Box 226, Folder 13)
    - Expenses (2 of 2), 1956-1958 (Box 226, Folder 14)
    - Family History, 1976 (Box 226, Folder 15)
    - The First Century of Scottish Rite Masonry Texas 1867-1967 (Box 226, Folder 16)
    - First Baptist Church Austin, TX Notes (1 of 2), undated (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - First Baptist Church Austin, TX Notes (2 of 2), undated (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - First Baptist Church Oklahoma City Illustrations, Vol. VI (1 of 3), undated (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - First Baptist Church Oklahoma City Illustrations, Vol. VI (2 of 3), undated (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - First Baptist Church Oklahoma City Illustrations, Vol. VI (3 of 3), undated (Box 227, Folder 5)
    - Football Tickets, 1960 (Box 227, Folder 6)
    - Form Letters by Dr. White, 1953-1955 (Box 227, Folder 7)
    - Gambling, 1962-1964 (Box 227, Folder 8)
    - Gifts and Donations, 1961 (Box 227, Folder 9)
    - Government Literary Productions, 1950-1951 (Box 227, Folder 10)
    - Heritage and Goals of Texas, undated (Box 227, Folder 11)
    - Itinerary, 1959-1960 (Box 227, Folder 12)
    - Income Tax, 1950-1951 (Box 227, Folder 13)
    - Income Tax (1 of 2), 1952 (Box 227, Folder 14)
    - Income Tax (2 of 2), 1952 (Box 227, Folder 15)
    - Income Tax Information, 1952 (Box 227, Folder 16)
    - Income Tax, 1953 (Box 227, Folder 17)
    - Income Tax, 1953-1955 (Box 227, Folder 18)
    - Income Tax Information, 1954-1955 (Box 227, Folder 19)
    - Income Tax Information (1 of 2), 1955 (Box 228, Folder 1)
    - Income Tax Information (2 of 2), 1955 (Box 228, Folder 2)
    - Income Tax, 1956 (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - Insurance, 1952 (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - Insurance, 1953 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - Insurance, 1954-1955 (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - Insurance 1, 1961 (Box 228, Folder 7)
    - Insurance 2, 1961 (Box 228, Folder 8)
    - Insurance Policies, Dr. White, 1950 (Box 228, Folder 9)
    - Investments, 1961 (Box 228, Folder 10)
    - Investors Mutual, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 228, Folder 11)
    - Israel (1 of 3), undated (Box 228, Folder 12)
    - Israel (2 of 3), undated (Box 228, Folder 13)
    - Israel (3 of 3), undated (Box 228, Folder 14)
    - Israel (1 of 4), 1958 (Box 228, Folder 15)
    - Israel (2 of 4), 1958 (Box 228, Folder 16)
    - Israel (3 of 4), 1958 (Box 228, Folder 17)
    - Israel (4 of 4), 1958 (Box 228, Folder 18)
    - Jewish Literature, 1960 (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - Life Insurance, undated (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - Lindsey, Harold E.-Sermon, undated (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - Liquor Bill, 1952 (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - Liquor Bill (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 229, Folder 5)
    - Liquor Bill (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 229, Folder 6)
    - List of Titles in Filing Cabinet, undated (Box 229, Folder 7)
    - Magazines (1 of 3), 1960-1961 (Box 229, Folder 8)
    - Magazines (2 of 3), 1960-1961 (Box 229, Folder 9)
    - Magazines (3 of 3), 1960-1961 (Box 229, Folder 10)
    - Messages, 1949 (Box 229, Folder 11)
    - Mental Health (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 229, Folder 12)
    - Mental Health (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 229, Folder 13)
    - Mental Health (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 229, Folder 14)
    - Mental Health (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 229, Folder 15)
    - Mixed (Statements and Receipts), 1960-1961 (Box 229, Folder 16)
    - Mixed (Receipts and Statements), 1960-1961 (Box 229, Folder 17)
    - New York Trip, 1951 (Box 229, Folder 18)
    - Newspaper Clippings-Politics (1 of 2), 1960 (Box 229, Folder 19)
    - Newspaper Clippings-Politics (2 of 2), 1960 (Box 229, Folder 20)
    - November, 1960 (Box 229, Folder 21)
    - October, 1960 (Box 229, Folder 22)
    - October, 1960 (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Paisano Baptist Encampment, undated (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - Passes-Trains, etc., 1949-1951 (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - Permanent Clippings (1 of 2), 1958-1967 (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - Permanent Clippings (2 of 2), 1958-1967 (Box 230, Folder 5)
    - Personal, 1962-1972 (Box 230, Folder 6)
    - Pictures, undated (Box 230, Folder 7)
    - Political (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 230, Folder 8)
    - Political (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 230, Folder 9)
    - Political Information on Communism (1 of 4), undated (Box 230, Folder 10)
    - Political Information on Communism (2 of 4), undated (Box 230, Folder 11)
    - Political Information on Communism (3 of 4), undated (Box 230, Folder 12)
    - Political Information on Communism (4 of 4), undated (Box 230, Folder 13)
    - Political Material for Carr P. Collins, undated (Box 230, Folder 14)
    - President White: Pictures, undated (Box 230, Folder 15)
    - Printed Travel Information, 1960 (Box 230, Folder 16)
    - Programs, undated (Box 230, Folder 17)
    - Programs (1 of 4), 1953 (Box 230, Folder 18)
    - Programs (2 of 4), 1953 (Box 231, Folder 1)
    - Programs (3 of 4), 1953 (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - Programs (4 of 4), 1953 (Box 231, Folder 3)
    - Programs (1 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 231, Folder 4)
    - Programs (2 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 231, Folder 5)
    - Programs (3 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 231, Folder 6)
    - Programs, 1955-1956 (Box 231, Folder 7)
    - Programs, 1956-1957 (Box 231, Folder 8)
    - Publicity-Dr. White (1 of 3), 1950-1951 (Box 231, Folder 9)
    - Publicity-Dr. White (2 of 3), 1950-1951 (Box 231, Folder 10)
    - Publicity-Dr. White (3 of 3), 1950-1951 (Box 231, Folder 11)
    - Race Track, Liquor, Communism, Atom, Delinquency (1 of 4), 1946-1947 (Box 231, Folder 12)
    - Race Track, Liquor, Communism, Atom, Delinquency (2 of 4), 1946-1947 (Box 231, Folder 13)
    - Race Track, Liquor, Communism, Atom, Delinquency (3 of 4), 1946-1947 (Box 231, Folder 14)
    - Race Track, Liquor, Communism, Atom, Delinquency (4 of 4), 1946-1947 (Box 231, Folder 15)
    - Racial Issues, 1961 (Box 231, Folder 16)
    - Robb Case, 1949 (Box 231, Folder 17)
    - Sisk, W.J. (1 of 3), 1962 (Box 231, Folder 18)
    - Sisk, W.J. (2 of 3), 1962 (Box 231, Folder 19)
    - Sisk, W.J. (3 of 3), 1962 (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Scriptures (1 of 6), 1948 (Box 232, Folder 2)
    - Scriptures (2 of 6), 1948 (Box 232, Folder 3)
    - Scriptures (3 of 6), 1948 (Box 232, Folder 4)
    - Scriptures (4 of 6), 1948 (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - Scriptures (5 of 6), 1948 (Box 232, Folder 6)
    - Scriptures (6 of 6), 1948 (Box 232, Folder 7)
    - Segregation (1 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 232, Folder 8)
    - Segregation (2 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 232, Folder 9)
    - Socialism, 1960 (Box 232, Folder 10)
    - South America, 1964 May 21-July 1 (Box 232, Folder 11)
    - Southland Life Insurance, 1960 (Box 232, Folder 12)
    - State Comptroller of Texas Robert S. Calvert, 1949-1950 (Box 232, Folder 13)
    - State Fair Park, 1955 (Box 232, Folder 14)
    - State Fair Park, 1956 (Box 232, Folder 15)
    - State Fair of Texas, 1956-1957 (Box 232, Folder 16)
    - Statesmanship Entertainment Education Culture, undated (Box 232, Folder 17)
    - Statements and Bills, 1951-1952 (Box 232, Folder 18)
    - Statements and Bills, 1953 (Box 232, Folder 19)
    - Statement Concerning Texas Tech and University of Houston, 1956 (Box 232, Folder 20)
    - Texas House Journal (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 232, Folder 21)
    - Texas House Journal (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 232, Folder 22)
    - Thornhill, T. J., 1948 (Box 232, Folder 23)
    - Topics Mixed (1 of 4), 1961-1963 (Box 232, Folder 24)
    - Topics Mixed (2 of 4), 1961-1963 (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Topics Mixed (3 of 4), 1961-1963 (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - Topics Mixed (4 of 4), 1961-1963 (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - Trip to New York City (1 of 3), 1960 October (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - Trip to New York City (2 of 3), 1960 October (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - Trip to New York City (3 of 3), 1960 October (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - Trip to the Orient Welcome Poster, undated (Box 285 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Union Bank Insurance, Co., 1960-1961 (Box 233, Folder 7)
    - Un-named (Physical Exam), 1948-1949 (Box 233, Folder 8)
    - Waco News-Tribune, 1959 March 18 (Box 285 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Waco News-Tribune, 1964 October 21 (Box 285 OVZ, Folder 11)
    - War on Drugs-Anti-Alcohol Material, undated (Box 233, Folder 9)
    - W.R. White (1 of 4), undated (Box 233, Folder 10)
    - W.R. White (2 of 4), undated (Box 233, Folder 11)
    - W.R. White (3 of 4), undated (Box 233, Folder 12)
    - W.R. White (4 of 4), undated (Box 233, Folder 13)
    - W.R. White Lecture Fund, 1961 (Box 233, Folder 14)
    - W.R. White-Personal, undated (Box 233, Folder 15)
    - W.R. White-Personal (1 of 5), undated (Box 233, Folder 16)
    - W.R. White-Personal (2 of 5), undated (Box 233, Folder 17)
    - W.R. White-Personal (3 of 5), undated (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - W.R. White-Personal (4 of 5), undated (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - W.R. White-Personal (5 of 5), undated (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Dr. White (1 of 2), 1946 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - Dr. White (2 of 2), 1946 (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - White-Expense Account (1 of 2), 1950-1951 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - White-Expense Account (2 of 2), 1950-1951 (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - White’s Banking Settlement, 1977 March (Box 234, Folder 8)
    - White’s Travel Material, undated (Box 234, Folder 9)
    - Dr. White’s Survey, 1962 (Box 234, Folder 10)
    - Who’s Who In America, undated (Box 234, Folder 11)
    - XYZ, 1947 (Box 234, Folder 12)
- Memberships and Affiliations, 1945-1968, undated; 4
  This is a paper collection of records from the various organizations where White held a membership or administrative position. Notable organizations include The Boy Scouts, Bishop College, and Mid-Western University. This subseries is arranged alphabetically.
  - Academy of Achievement, undated (Box 234, Folder 13)
  - Alcohol, Mixed, 1958-1959 (Box 234, Folder 14)
  - Alcohol, Mixed, 1959 (Box 234, Folder 15)
  - American Council on Education, 1957-1958 (Box 234, Folder 16)
  - American Council on Education (1 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 234, Folder 17)
  - American Council on Education (2 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 234, Folder 18)
  - The Bulletin of The American Association of Fundraising Counsel, 1960 (Box 234, Folder 19)
  - The American Association of Theological Schools—Materials Submitted to Committee of the Accrediting Commission (1 of 3), 1958 (Box 234, Folder 20)
  - The American Association of Theological Schools—Materials Submitted to Committee of the Accrediting Commission (2 of 3), 1958 (Box 234, Folder 21)
  - The American Association of Theological Schools—Materials Submitted to Committee of the Accrediting Commission (3 of 3), 1958 (Box 234, Folder 22)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1960 (Box 234, Folder 23)
  - American Association of University Women, 1960 (Box 234, Folder 24)
  - American Cancer Society, Inc., 1961 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1959-1960 (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1961-1962 (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - American Council on Education (1 of 7), 1948-1951 (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - American Council on Education (2 of 7), 1948-1951 (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - American Council on Education (3 of 7), 1948-1951 (Box 235, Folder 6)
  - American Council on Education (4 of 7), 1948-1951 (Box 235, Folder 7)
  - American Council on Education (5 of 7), 1948-1951 (Box 235, Folder 8)
  - American Council on Education (6 of 7), 1948-1951 (Box 235, Folder 9)
  - American Council on Education (7 of 7), 1948-1951 (Box 235, Folder 10)
  - American Council on Education, 1951-1952 (Box 235, Folder 11)
  - American Council on Education, 1953 (Box 235, Folder 12)
  - American Council on Education (1 of 3), 1954 (Box 235, Folder 13)
  - American Council on Education (2 of 3), 1954 (Box 235, Folder 14)
  - American Council on Education (3 of 3), 1954 (Box 235, Folder 15)
  - American Council on Education (1 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 235, Folder 16)
  - American Council on Education (2 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 235, Folder 17)
  - American Council on Education, 1959 (Box 235, Folder 18)
  - American Council on Education (1 of 3), 1961 (Box 235, Folder 19)
  - American Council on Education (2 of 3), 1961 (Box 235, Folder 20)
  - American Council on Education (3 of 3), 1961 (Box 235, Folder 21)
  - American Council on Education (1 of 2), 1961-1963 (Box 235, Folder 22)
  - American Council on Education (2 of 2), 1961-1963 (Box 235, Folder 23)
  - Annuity Board, 1960 (Box 235, Folder 24)
  - Annuity Board, 1961 (Box 235, Folder 25)
  - The Argyle, 1957 (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - The Argyle (1 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - The Argyle (2 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - The Argyle, 1959-1960 (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - Association of American Colleges (1 of 2), 1949-1951 (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - Association of American Colleges (2 of 2), 1949-1951 (Box 236, Folder 6)
  - Association of Southern Baptist for Scouting Report (1 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 236, Folder 7)
  - Association of Southern Baptist for Scouting Report (2 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 236, Folder 8)
  - Association of Texas Colleges Bulletin, 1956 May (Box 236, Folder 9)
  - Association of Texas Graduate Schools, 1962 (Box 236, Folder 10)
  - Association Mixed, 1963 (Box 236, Folder 11)
  - Atomic Energy (1 of 6), 1946-1947 (Box 236, Folder 12)
  - Atomic Energy (2 of 6), 1946-1947 (Box 236, Folder 13)
  - Atomic Energy (3 of 6), 1946-1947 (Box 236, Folder 14)
  - Atomic Energy (4 of 6), 1946-1947 (Box 236, Folder 15)
  - Atomic Energy (5 of 6), 1946-1947 (Box 236, Folder 16)
  - Atomic Energy (6 of 6), 1946-1947 (Box 236, Folder 17)
  - Baptist Capital Needs Campaign, undated (Box 236, Folder 18)
  - Baptist Convention New Mexico-Expenses, 1951 (Box 236, Folder 19)
  - Baptist Education Study Commission (1 of 3), 1967, 1975 (Box 236, Folder 20)
  - Baptist Education Study Commission (2 of 3), 1967, 1975 (Box 236, Folder 21)
  - Baptist Education Study Commission (3 of 3), 1967, 1975 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas (1 of 2), 1945-1949 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas (2 of 2), 1945-1949 (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Baptist Foundation, 1957 (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - Baptist Foundation, 1958 (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Baptist Foundation (1 of 2), 1959 (Box 237, Folder 6)
  - Baptist Foundation (2 of 2), 1959 (Box 237, Folder 7)
  - Baptist Foundation (1 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 237, Folder 8)
  - Baptist Foundation (2 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 237, Folder 9)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas (1 of 2), 1962 May 10-11 (Box 237, Folder 10)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas (2 of 2), 1962 May 10-11 (Box 237, Folder 11)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas-Pastors’ Day, 1973 Fall (Box 237, Folder 12)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1951-1952 (Box 237, Folder 13)
  - Baptist General Convention (1 of 2), 1954-1955 (Box 237, Folder 14)
  - Baptist General Convention (2 of 2), 1954-1955 (Box 237, Folder 15)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas (1 of 2), 1957-1958 (Box 237, Folder 16)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas (2 of 2), 1957-1958 (Box 237, Folder 17)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1958-1960 (Box 237, Folder 18)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1961 (Box 237, Folder 19)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1965 (Box 237, Folder 20)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas Literary Productions (1 of 2), undated (Box 237, Folder 21)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas Literary Productions (2 of 2), undated (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - Baptist Missions-Missions 9-10 List of Foreign Mission Societies (1 of 6), undated (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - Baptist Missions-Missions 9-10 List of Foreign Mission Societies (2 of 6), undated (Box 238, Folder 3)
  - Baptist Missions-Missions 9-10 List of Foreign Mission Societies (3 of 6), undated (Box 238, Folder 4)
  - Baptist Missions-Missions 9-10 List of Foreign Mission Societies (4 of 6), undated (Box 238, Folder 5)
  - Baptist Missions-Missions 9-10 List of Foreign Mission Societies (5 of 6), undated (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - Baptist Missions-Missions 9-10 List of Foreign Mission Societies (6 of 6), undated (Box 238, Folder 7)
  - Baptist Review, 1961 (Box 238, Folder 8)
  - Baptist Standard, 1950 (Box 238, Folder 9)
  - Baptist World Alliance—Commission on Religious Liberty and Human Rights, 1961 (Box 238, Folder 10)
  - Baptist World Alliance (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 238, Folder 11)
  - Baptist World Alliance (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 238, Folder 12)
  - Baptist World Alliance, 1962 (Box 238, Folder 13)
  - Bishop College-President’s Report, 1948 (Box 238, Folder 14)
  - Bishop College-President’s Report, 1949 (Box 238, Folder 15)
  - Bishop College (1 of 3), 1951 (Box 238, Folder 16)
  - Bishop College (2 of 3), 1951 (Box 238, Folder 17)
  - Bishop College (3 of 3), 1951 (Box 238, Folder 18)
  - Bishop College (1 of 3), 1952 (Box 238, Folder 19)
  - Bishop College (2 of 3), 1952 (Box 238, Folder 20)
  - Bishop College (3 of 3), 1952 (Box 238, Folder 21)
  - Bishop College-Special President’s Report (1 of 2), 1952 (Box 238, Folder 22)
  - Bishop College-Special President’s Report (2 of 2), 1952 (Box 238, Folder 23)
  - Bishop College-Board Minutes for 1952 (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - Bishop College (1 of 5), 1952-1953 (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - Bishop College (2 of 5), 1952-1953 (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Bishop College (3 of 5), 1952-1953 (Box 239, Folder 4)
  - Bishop College (4 of 5), 1952-1953 (Box 239, Folder 5)
  - Bishop College (5 of 5), 1952-1953 (Box 239, Folder 6)
  - Bishop College-Report of the President (1 of 2), 1953 April 22 (Box 239, Folder 7)
  - Bishop College-Report of the President (2 of 2), 1953 April 22 (Box 239, Folder 8)
  - Bishop College-Annual Report (1 of 2), 1953 (Box 239, Folder 9)